<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Scientific Computing @ Emory on Emory Scientific Computing Group</title>
    <link>http://www.mathcs.emory.edu/Research/Area/ScientificComputing/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Scientific Computing @ Emory on Emory Scientific Computing Group</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>&amp;copy; All rights reserved.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 28 Aug 2017 09:27:03 -0400</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://www.mathcs.emory.edu/Research/Area/ScientificComputing/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Schedule</title>
      <link>http://www.mathcs.emory.edu/Research/Area/ScientificComputing/schedule/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Aug 2017 09:49:04 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.mathcs.emory.edu/Research/Area/ScientificComputing/schedule/</guid>
      <description>Meetings of the Scientific Computing Group will be held once a week, 2:00&amp;ndash;3:00 in W301. The meetings will usually be on Friday, but occasionally we will meet at other times. For specifics, see the schedule below.
Some food (e.g., pizza) will normally be provided once every month, and participants are welcome to bring their own lunch to other meetings. Entertainment will normally consist of a seminar talk.
First year graduate students and undergraduates interested in scientific computing are welcome to attend.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>People</title>
      <link>http://www.mathcs.emory.edu/Research/Area/ScientificComputing/people/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Aug 2017 09:35:08 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.mathcs.emory.edu/Research/Area/ScientificComputing/people/</guid>
      <description> Faculty  Michele Benzi Bree Ettinger Manuela Manetta James Nagy Lars Ruthotto Vaidy Sunderam Alessandro Veneziani  Adjunct Faculty  Mario Arioli Maxim Olshanskii Zdenek Strakos  Long Term Visitors  James Nance  Postdocs  Boyi Yang Adrien Lefieux  Graduate Students  Alessandro Barone Ricardo Bonilla Samy Wu Fung Clarissa Garvey Sofia Guzzetti James Herring Yunyi Hu Ru Huang Chang Meng Derek Onken Massimiliano Lupo Pasini Blair Rosetti Alex Viguerie Huijuan Xu  Visiting Graduate Students  Ludovico Bruni Bruno  Undergraduate Honors Students  Huiying Zhu  Former Long Term Visitors  Mario Arioli Fatemeh Panjeh Ali Beik Margaret Callahan Ernesto Estrada Bao Liang Jan Modersitzki Maxim Olshanskii Annalisa Quaini Leo Rebholz Zdenek Strakos Jianjun Zhang  Former Postdocs  Gaetano Esposito (2014-2015) Leandro Gryngarten (2013-2014) Lina Merchan (2013-2014) Tiziano Passerini (2009-2013) Paola Boito (2009-2010) Matthias Chung (2008-2010) Luca Gerardo-Giorda (2008-2010) Lucia Mirabella (2008-2010) Mauro Perego (2008-2010) Lior Horesh (2007&amp;ndash;2009) Stefan Heldmann (2006&amp;ndash;2008) Bora Ucar (2005&amp;ndash;2006)  Former Graduate Students  Isabel Chen, PhD 2016 Huanhuan Yang, PhD 2015 Boyi Yang, PhD 2015 Sebastian Berisha, PhD 2014 Luca Bertagna, PhD 2014 Qing Chu, PhD 2014 Anastasia Svischeva, PhD 2014 Christine Klymko, PhD 2014 Alexis Aposporidis, PhD 2013 Verena Kuhlemann, PhD 2013 Veronica Mejia-Bustamante, PhD 2013 Umberto Villa, PhD 2013 Marta D&amp;rsquo;Elia, PhD 2012 Steven Hamilton, PhD 2011 Sarah Knepper, PhD 2011 Zhuojun Tang Magnant, PhD 2011 Zhen Wang, PhD 2011 Raya Horesh, PhD 2010 Ying Wai (Daniel) Fan, PhD 2010 Piotr Wendykier, PhD 2009 Julianne Chung, PhD 2009 Nader Razouk, PhD 2008 Lauren Hanson, PhD 2007 Dawid Kurzyniec, PhD 2007 Jia Liu, PhD 2006 Kiandra Johnson, MS 2005 Katrina Palmer, PhD 2004 Lisa Perrone, PhD 2004  Former Visiting Graduate Students  Francesca Arrigo Anastasia Cornelio Caterina Fenu Silvia Gazzola Marie Kubinova Adrien Lefieux Johannes Lotz Maximilian Marz Jan Macdonald Marina Piccinelli Helen Schomburg  Former Undergraduate Honors Students  Yiwen Guo, BS 2017 Raul Platero, BS 2017 Hanyong Wu, BS 2017 Claire Lin, BS 2016 Lu Lin, BS 2016 Chang Meng, BS 2016 Sid Raju, BS 2016 Tianli Han, BS 2015 Hanqiu Xia, BS 2015 Brian Breeden, BS 2014 Shannon Buckley, BS 2014 Ngoc Hoang Lam Phan, BS 2014 Kexin Qu, BS 2014 Yuan Ye, BS 2014 Chen (Cool) Cheng, BS 2013 Warrick Macmillan, BS 2013 Yifan Wang, BS 2013 Josh Keller, BS 2011 James Nance, BS 2011 Ruth Blum, BS 2010 James Herring, BS 2010 Melissa Goldstein, BS 2006 Julianne Chung, BA 2004 Mili Shah, BS/MS 2002 Ryan Wright, BS/MS 2002 Sharriah Sulaiman, BS/MS 2001  </description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>